[
    {
        "question": "The student asked, \"Is the sky blue ?\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "asked",
          "1": "blue",
          "3": "the",
          "2": "the",
          "5": "was",
          "6": "if",
          "7": "sky",
          "8": "student",
          "9": "that",
          "10": "is"
        },
        "answers":[[2,8,4,6,3,7,10,1],[3,8,4,6,2,7,10,1]]
    },
    {
        "question": "The student said, \"Was Akbar a good emperor ?\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "enquired",
          "1": "been",
          "3": "emperor",
          "2": "was",
          "5": "a",
          "6": "the",
          "7": "had",
          "8": "if",
          "9": "good",
          "10": "Akbar",
          "11": "student"
        },
        "answers":[[6,11,4,8,10,7,1,5,9,3]]
    },
    {
        "question": "He says, \"Were you going to school that day ?\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "school",
          "1": "whether",
          "3": "been",
          "2": "I",
          "5": "he",
          "6": "that",
          "7": "to",
          "8": "had",
          "9": "asks",
          "10": "going",
          "11": "day",
          "12": "was"
        },
        "answers":[[5,9,1,2,8,3,10,7,4,6,11]]
    },
    {
        "question": "His angry mother shouted, \"Do you think that you know better than your father ?\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "his father",
          "1": "mother",
          "3": "than",
          "2": "that",
          "5": "and",
          "6": "known",
          "7": "he",
          "8": "his",
          "9": "he",
          "10": "better",
          "11": "asked",
          "12": "shouted",
          "13": "thought",
          "14": "knew",
          "15": "angry",
          "16": "if"
        },
        "answers":[[8,15,1,12,5,11,16,9,13,2,7,14,10,3,4],[8,15,1,12,5,11,16,7,13,2,9,14,10,3,4]]
    },
    {
        "question": "The policeman said to us, \"Go away.\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "policeman",
          "1": "that",
          "3": "us",
          "2": "the",
          "5": "to",
          "6": "ordered",
          "7": "away",
          "8": "asked",
          "9": "go"
        },
        "answers":[[2,4,6,3,5,9,7]]
    },
    {
        "question": "I told him, \"Please wait here till I return.\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "I",
          "1": "him",
          "3": "there",
          "2": "to",
          "5": "I",
          "6": "asked",
          "7": "returned",
          "8": "wait",
          "9": "requested",
          "10": "till",
          "11": "here"
        },
        "answers":[[4,9,1,2,8,3,10,5,7]]
    },
    {
        "question": "The mother said to her son, \"Eat your food now.\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "told",
          "1": "eat",
          "3": "her",
          "2": "his",
          "5": "right",
          "6": "the",
          "7": "son",
          "8": "asked",
          "9": "to",
          "10": "food",
          "11": "then",
          "12": "mother",
          "13": "now"
        },
        "answers":[[6,12,4,3,7,9,1,2,10,5,11]]
    },
    {
        "question": "The teacher said, \"Sit down, boys.\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "boys",
          "1": "asked",
          "3": "the",
          "2": "to",
          "5": "down",
          "6": "teacher",
          "7": "requested",
          "8": "sit",
          "9": "the",
          "10": "that"
        },
        "answers":[[9,6,1,3,4,2,8,5],[3,6,1,9,4,2,8,5]]
    },
    {
        "question": "The leader said, \"Be quiet and listen to my words.\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "asked",
          "1": "listen",
          "3": "be",
          "2": "requested",
          "5": "the",
          "6": "them",
          "7": "his",
          "8": "and",
          "9": "to",
          "10": "quiet",
          "11": "leader",
          "12": "words",
          "13": "to"
        },
        "answers":[[5,11,4,6,13,3,10,8,1,9,7,12],[5,11,4,6,9,3,10,8,1,13,7,12]]
    },
    {
        "question": "She told me, \"Please help me.\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "asked",
          "1": "me",
          "3": "her",
          "2": "please",
          "5": "to",
          "6": "requested",
          "7": "help",
          "8": "she"
        },
        "answers":[[8,6,1,5,7,3]]
    },
    {
        "question": "My friend said, \"Can you close the window please ?\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "requested",
          "1": "that",
          "3": "close",
          "2": "my",
          "5": "me",
          "6": "asked",
          "7": "window",
          "8": "friend",
          "9": "to",
          "10": "the"
        },
        "answers":[[2,8,4,5,9,3,10,7]]
    },
    {
        "question": "The doctor said, \"Don't smoke.\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "the",
          "1": "asked",
          "3": "to",
          "2": "don't",
          "5": "doctor",
          "6": "smoke",
          "7": "requested",
          "8": "not"
        },
        "answers":[[4,5,1,8,3,6]]
    },
    {
        "question": "The judge said to all, \"Be on time.\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "ordered",
          "1": "be",
          "3": "the",
          "2": "on",
          "5": "requested",
          "6": "all",
          "7": "time",
          "8": "judge",
          "9": "to"
        },
        "answers":[[3,8,4,6,9,1,2,7]]
    },
    {
        "question": "The prisoner shouted, \"Let me go.\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "begged",
          "1": "prisoner",
          "3": "said",
          "2": "let",
          "5": "the",
          "6": "and",
          "7": "go",
          "8": "to",
          "9": "him",
          "10": "shouted"
        },
        "answers":[[5,1,10,6,4,8,2,9,7]]
    }
]